Report!
Your Majesty, rebels have launched a surprise attack in the capital.
They are coming in full force.
What?
How could this happen?
This is too sudden.
Yue.
Go to Yan's palace first.
Please be careful.
You be careful too.
Don't worry.
Logically,
the Grand Princess has already been imprisoned.
Why are there still rebels?
I remember this game.
Different actions will trigger different storylines.
Maybe it was triggered accidentally.
What a crappy storyline.
It had to trigger during my wedding.
Couldn't it wait until I was done?
What's so good about this crappy wedding of yours?
I wonder where these rebels came from.
By the way, Jingyuan,
you joined this game earlier than I did.
Didn't you meet other players
to know the storyline in advance?
They usually die in the first level.
It was in the second episode where you met Si Xingxuan.
But Si Xingxuan wouldn't kill anyone.
But Eunuch Sun could.
Otherwise, how do you think
he got the title of tyrant?
What's that smell?
Oh no.
Enduring hardships for ten years,
I have finally waited for this day.
Fan Ying?
Aren't you Si Xinglan's male favorite?
Why are you here?
What are you going to do?
You killed my Lan'er,
so of course I am here to avenge her.
Avenge?
How about you wait a few days
until Si Xingxuan and I get married?
Are you okay?
To tell you the truth,
I was the youngest and most promising
high priest of the Ancient Wu Tribe,
with a boundless future.
Donglin wiped out my entire tribe,
forcing me to become a male favorite.
I could only hide beside Si Xinglan,
helping her refine Gu poison.
I did it all so that this world
would become the world of my Ancient Wu Tribe.
So you were the one who poisoned Xingyao and Axuan with Gu.
That's right.
If that fool Si Xinglan hadn't forced the emperor to abdicate without permission,
ruining my years of planning,
I would have been the emperor long ago.
What are you guys playing?
Untie me quickly.
I need to pee.
Shut up!
What can you do by tying us up?
You can't defeat him.
Now you've fallen into my
trap of luring the tiger out of the mountain.
With the three of you held here,
Si Xingxuan will definitely come to rescue you.
If he enters this palace,
he will surely become a rat in a trap,
at my mercy.
Lord Fan, Si Xingxuan and his troops
were stopped by us at the palace gate.
He's finally here.
Brother.
Trying to rescue them single-handedly.
Playing the hero.
Kill!
I want to see how long you can last.
Still won't surrender?
Si Xingxuan.
You hid it well.
Good martial arts.
Good.
It's good that you're here.
Let the three of them go.
Wait, why?
Since Si Xingxuan is here,
our goal is achieved.
We only have a grudge against the Donglin royal family.
We can't kill the innocent.
Let them go.
Then what about that prince?
Isn't he also a member of the royal family?
Why let him go?
He's just a fool.
You're the fool.
Watch out!
Yuanyuan!
Jingyuan!
Yuanyuan, what's wrong with you?
You're bleeding!
Yuanyuan!
Yuanyuan,
you're bleeding.
A'yan, I'm fine.
No, no.
A'yan,
I won't be able to take care of you anymore.
No, no.
A'yan, from now on, in this world,
you must
take good care of yourself.
No, no.
Brother Yuanyuan, Brother Jingyuan!
Jingyuan, don't leave me.
Please don't leave me.
Since you managed to break into the palace,
I want to see exactly what you are capable of.
Stand down.
So many brothers died today.
I will settle this with him alone.
Alright.
I will oblige you.